(crowd cheering)
(upbeat rock music)
♪ Just a small town girl ♪
♪ Livin' in a lonely world ♪
♪ She took the midnight
train going anywhere ♪
♪ Just a city boy ♪
♪ Born and raised in Houston ♪
♪ He took the midnight
train going anywhere ♪
Neal!
♪ A singer in a smokey room ♪
♪ A smell of wine and cheap perfume ♪
♪ For a smile they can share the night ♪
♪ It goes on and on and on and on ♪
Come on!
♪ Strangers waitin' ♪
♪ Up and down the boulevard ♪
♪ Their shadows searchin' in the night ♪
♪ Streetlights, people ♪
♪ Livin' just to find emotion ♪
♪ Hidin', somewhere in the night ♪
♪ Workin' hard to get my fill ♪
♪ Everybody wants a thrill ♪
♪ Payin' anything to roll the dice ♪
♪ Just one more time ♪
♪ Some'll win, some will lose ♪
♪ Some are born to sing the blues ♪
♪ Whoa, the movie never ends ♪
♪ It goes on and on and on and on ♪
C'mon Houston!
♪ Strangers waitin' ♪
♪ Up and down the boulevard ♪
♪ Their shadows searchin' in the night ♪
♪ Streetlights, people ♪
♪ Livin' to find emotion ♪
♪ Hidin', somewhere in the night ♪
♪ Don't stop believin' ♪
♪ Hold on to that feelin' ♪
♪ Streetlights, people ♪
♪ Don't stop believin' ♪
♪ Hold on ♪
♪ Streetlights, people ♪
♪ Don't stop believin' ♪
♪ Hold on Houston to your feelin' ♪
♪ Streetlights, people ♪
♪ Don't stop ♪
(crowd cheering)